There were some fans that thought
有一些球迷认为
I had something to do with Avengers: Endgame.
我跟复仇者联盟：终结游戏。
(audience laughs)
（观众笑）
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Taylor Swift defeated Thanos?
泰勒 · 斯威夫特击败了塔诺斯？
Not quite.
不完全是。
Taylor made her first appearance on The Ellen DeGeneres Show
泰勒做了她的第一次出现在艾伦 · 德杰尼勒斯显示
in four years on Wednesday.
在周三四年。
And opened up about how she leaves Easter eggs
并打开了她如何离开复活节彩蛋
for her Swifties in her music videos,
为她的音乐视频中的斯威夫人，
and her interviews, and basically everywhere,
和她的采访，基本上无处不在，
because she loves making us lose our minds.
因为她喜欢让我们失去理智。
But with all that sleuthing and speculating,
但是，随着所有的昏睡和猜测，
we Swifties can't get it right every time.
我们斯威夫斯不能每次都得到正确的。
So, Ellen asked the "Me" singer just how far off
所以，艾伦问 “我” 歌手只是多远
her fans have been with something they thought
她的粉丝一直与他们认为的东西
was and Easter egg, but totally wasn't.
和复活节彩蛋，但完全不是。
T-Swift called to mind when
T-斯威夫特叫介意时
some Swifties thought she might have something to do
有些 Swifties 认为她可能有事情要做
with Avengers: Endgame.
与复仇者: 终结游戏.
Because we had the single coming out the same day
因为同一天就出来了
and I have a song that was called Endgame,
我有一首歌，叫做终结游戏，
and so they were like, oh my God, she's gonna defeat Thanos.
所以他们就像，哦，我的上帝，她要打败塔诺斯。
(audience laughs)
（观众笑）
I let everyone down. Yeah, yeah.
我让每个人都失望。 是啊，是啊。
Again.
再来一次
As a Swiftie, I'm just glad she didn't call us out
作为一名斯威夫蒂，我很高兴她没有叫我们出去
for the whole five holes in the fence theory again.
在围栏理论的整个五个洞。
During her appearance on the talk show,
在她出现在脱口秀节目中，
Tay also played a round of burning questions.
泰也打了一轮燃烧的问题。
Where she opened up about her favorite T.V. shows,
在那里她打开了她最喜欢的电视节目，
her favorite movies she saw this week,
她最喜欢的电影，她看了这个星期，
and addressed one of her most memorable Ellen Show moments.
并谈到她最难忘的艾伦秀时刻之一.
When the host asked Taylor about the most
当主机问泰勒有关最
rebellious thing she did as a teenager,
叛逆的事情，她做了一个十几岁，
the singer/songwriter said this.
歌手/词曲作者这样说。
Probably when I like put Joe Jonas on blast on your show.
也许当我喜欢让乔乔纳斯在你的节目上爆炸。
(audience laughs)
（观众笑）
That was too much.
太过分了
Was it? Yeah.
是吗？ 是啊。
Of course Taylor was referencing this
当然，泰勒引用了这个
iconic time in pop-culture history
流行文化史上的标志性时间
that was, if you can believe it, 11 years ago, in 2008.
那就是，如果你能相信的话，11 年前，在 2008 年。
And when I look at that person,
当我看着那个人，
I'm not even gonna be able to remember
我甚至都记不起来了
the boy who broke up with me over the phone
通过电话跟我分手的那个男孩
in 25 seconds when I was 18.
在 25 秒，当我 18。
(audience gasps)
（观众喘气）
Ooh, the shade was so real then.
哦，树荫是那么真实的。
But, Tay admitted she and the Jonas Brother
但是，泰承认她和乔纳斯兄弟
can laugh about it now.
现在可以笑它。
♪ I promise that you'll never ♪
♪ 我保证你永远 ♪
♪ Find another like me-e-e ♪
♪ 找到另一个像我-e-e ♪
All right for the full clips
所有的权利为完整的剪辑
from Taylor's appearance on Ellen, head to thr.com.
从泰勒在艾伦的外观, 头到 Thr.com.
Until next time, for The Hollywood Reporter News,
直到下一次，对于好莱坞记者新闻，
I'm Tiffany Taylor.
我是蒂芙尼 · 泰勒
(upbeat music)
（乐观的音乐）